harrypotterfanfiction.com 2012-06-15

# harrypotterfanfiction.com :: 74,000 Harry Potter fanfiction stories and podcasts

| 

_Privacy Policy_

Fanfictionworld.net privacy policy.

It is our policy that personal information given to us , such as your name and e-mail address, is private and confidential. As such, the personal information you provide is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provided the information, such as to register or as a point of contact. While this information will not be disclosed to any third party without your consent, the site owner, administrator and moderators cannot be held responsible for any hacking attempt that may lead to the data being compromised or corrupted. Please note that any email sent through the archive software may be periodically checked for abuse.

We will not release personal information to third parties. Except if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties.

Our network is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our site. This information is used only for internal purposes by our staff.

In addition, our website tracks information about the visits to our web site. For example, we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our site, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web site, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used to guage the popularity of the site, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. 

If you have any problem with privacy on this site, please use the [contact section](http://www.harrypotterfanfiction.com/getinfo.php?page=staffcontact) to mail a staff member.

| 

| 

All stories remain the property of their authors and must not be copied in any form without their consent. This is an unofficial, not for profit site, and is in no way connected with J.K. Rowling, Scholastic Books or Bloomsbury Publishing or Warner Bros. It is not endorsed by any of the aforementioned parties. Rights to characters and their images is neither claimed nor implied. The use of photographs and/or the likeness of any person contained herein does not imply endorsement of any kind. Any depictions were obtained through publically available sources and therefore fall under fair use. Although we may provide links to other websites, we are not responsible for any material at these sites. You acknowledge that you link to these other websites at your own risk. **All original administrative content is copyright of the site owner and must not be copied in any form (electronic or otherwise) without the prior consent of the siteowner.** ©2000-2012 Fanfictionworld.net

[[terms of service](http://www.harrypotterfanfiction.com/getinfo.php?page=tos)] [[report abuse](http://www.hpff.info/index.php?_m=tickets&_a=submit)] [[privacy policy](http://www.harrypotterfanfiction.com/getinfo.php?page=privacypolicy)] [[site credits](http://www.harrypotterfanfiction.com/getinfo.php?page=sitecredits)]
